Hey what's up guys it's Josh here with the School
of Hard Knocks. Hope you guys are having a great
day. Today we're talking all about how to upload
to Facebook Reels and how to get the maximum
amount of exposure from those Reels as well.
This is going to be a very straightforward
and actionable video just showing you how to get
it done. So I'm going to be hopping behind the
computer doing a screen recording and getting into
it. So if you guys enjoy content like this
where it just gives you actionable simple advice
that you can take action on, give a subscribe.
I would really appreciate it. Let's go ahead hop into
it. Just so you guys know this is the exact
same process on the mobile app as it is
on the desktop version. I'll be doing this example in
the mobile app. So you're going to want to go
ahead and log in and you're going to want to go
to your pages and then select the page that you want
to use. So I want to use the School of Hard
Knocks. So I'm going to go ahead and scroll down
and go to right here where you can create a post
and I'm going to go ahead and create a Reel
and you're going to go ahead and go to the bottom
left and select the
video that you want to use. I'm going to go
ahead and select this one right here asking a social
media expert and influencer the advice he gives
himself. And so typically what I found and I've
actually learned this from TikTok and creating content on
there is you always want to add a sound.
The reason being is because I have found in
my experiences that typically when you add a sound
that you genuinely just get more exposure for your
videos. So I'm going to go ahead, click on the
sound icon, add music and the music that
you typically want to add, whether you're going to
add a song or you want to listen to it or
not, is I like to add a trending sound slash artist. I'm
going to add Whoa by Lil Baby and because I
don't want to actually listen to the sound in my video,
I'm going to turn the volume all the way down just
so you can barely hear it. And so that way the
overall music or the overall sound of the video is
the same, but I still get the added benefits of
having the sound involved. So after I've added the
sound, I like to go ahead and change this timeline
bar to where I want to add the sound. So I'm
going to go ahead and click on the sound icon and then
I want to add the thumbnail slash the cover for this
reel to be. So I'm going to change it to right
here. Going to go to next. And so now that is
my cover for my reel. So for the description, I like
to add in some sort of call to action or
thought provoking question to get people to watch the full
amount of the video. So I typically lean towards
a call to action, getting people to follow. So you
get people to say, uh, follow for more content
like this. And then I'm going to go ahead and
like an emoji and you could do
something like that I recommend you experiment
with a bunch of different phrases
questions or just call to actions in
general and find what works for you
and what gets traction so after you've added
in your call to action you want to
add in a relevant hashtags to the post
itself as well as to the overall page
and niche of your business in general so
for this this is a social
media and then influencer because this directly
correlates to the title of the video and
then you want to add in so business
entrepreneur and like other stuff like
that because that's relevant to my page
itself because the school of hard
knocks is a business entrepreneurship and like
finance page right so you're gonna
add in typically six to seven hashtags
that's at least what I have been
doing and then after you've done all that
you're gonna want to go ahead and press
share the real and you're good to go
hopefully you guys enjoyed some of the
tips that I shared on uploading your
reels on a Facebook
ultimately I'm going to be posting a
video on Facebook and I'm going to be
posting videos on my Twitter and I'm going
to post my post there and I'll be
posting a video on Instagram and on
my Twitter but I personally think this
video should be just one part
of your brand strategy to build overall
awareness around your brand if you're
looking for more advanced and in-depth
tips this week I'll be uploading a guide
on how you can grow your brand on
social media if you enjoyed this video
please leave us a like and subscribe
would really appreciate it catch
you guys in the next one